<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.airytv" version="0.1.2" name="AiryTV" provider-name="Lunatixz">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.six" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" version="0.1.3.1"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.7.0"/> 
        <import addon="script.module.simplecache" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.routing" version="0.2.3"/>
        <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.3.3"/>
        <import addon="plugin.video.tubed" version="0.0.1"/>
        <import addon="service.iptv.manager" version="0.2.2" optional="true"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="pseudotv_recommended.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
        <source>https://github.com/Lunatixz/KODI_Addons/tree/master/plugin.video.airytv</source>
        <website>https://airy.tv/</website>
        <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=361486&amp;pid=3023875</forum>
        <news>v1.0.0[CR]- Matrix Support[CR]</news>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/images/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/images/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot01.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot02.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot03.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot04.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
        <summary lang="da_DK">Airy TV er underholdningsdestinationen for at se 100% gratis tv.</summary>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Airy TV is the entertainment destination for watching 100% Free TV.</summary>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Airy TV es el destino de entretenimiento para ver TV 100% gratis.</summary>
        <summary lang="fi_FI">Airy TV on viihdekohde 100 % ilmaiseen television katseluun.</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_FR">Airy TV est la destination de divertissement pour regarder la télévision 100% gratuite.</summary>
        <summary lang="it_IT">Airy TV è la meta del divertimento per guardare TV gratuita al 100%.</summary>
        <description lang="da_DK">Airy TV er underholdningsdestinationen for at se 100% gratis tv, film og komik. Stream anime og sport - al din underholdning på ét sted. Streaming har aldrig været nemmere! Airy TV har ingen kontrakt, ingen gebyrer, no-nonsense, kun gratis tv, film, komik, anime, sport - al din underholdning leveret til dig.</description>
        <description lang="en_GB">Airy TV is the entertainment destination for watching 100% Free TV, Movies &amp; Comedy. Stream Anime &amp; Sports, all your entertainment in one place. ... Streaming has never been smoother! Airy TV has no contract, no fees, no-nonsense, just free TV, Movies, Comedy Anime, Sports, all your entertainment delivered to you.</description>
        <description lang="es_ES">Airy TV es el destino de entretenimiento para ver TV, Películas y Comedia 100% Gratis. Transmisión de anime y deportes, todo su entretenimiento en un solo lugar. ... ¡La transmisión nunca ha sido tan suave! Airy TV no tiene contrato, sin cuotas, sin tonterías, sólo TV gratis, Películas, Comedia Anime, Deportes, todo su entretenimiento a su disposición.</description>
        <description lang="fi_FI">Airy TV on viihdekohde, josta voit katsoa televisiota, elokuvia ja komedioita 100 % ilmaiseksi. Suoratoista animea ja urheilua, kaikki viihteesi yhdessä paikassa. ... Suoratoisto ei ole koskaan ollut sujuvampaa! Airy TV ei sisällä sopimuksia, maksuja tai tyhjänpäiväisyyksiä, vaan yksinkertaisesti ilmaista televisiota, elokuvia, komedioita, animea, urheilua. Kaikki viihteesi sinulle toimitettuna.</description>
        <description lang="fr_FR">Airy TV est la destination de divertissement pour regarder la télévision, les films et les comédies 100% gratuits. Stream Anime &amp; Sports, tous vos divertissements en un seul endroit. ... Le streaming n&apos;a jamais été aussi fluide ! Airy TV n&apos;a pas de contrat, pas de frais, pas de problème, juste de la TV gratuite, des films, des comédies, de l&apos;animation, des sports, tous vos divertissements livrés à vous.</description>
        <description lang="it_IT">Airy TV è la meta del divertimento per guardare TV, film e commedie gratuiti al 100% . Trasmette anime e sport, tutto il tuo intrattenimento in un unico posto. La riproduzione non è mai stata così fluida! Airy TV non ha nessun contratto, nessuna tariffa, nessuna vincolo, solo TV gratuita: film, anime, sport, tutto il tuo intrattenimento ti viene consegnato a costo zero.</description>
    </extension>
</addon>