<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="screensaver.google.earth" name="Google Earth" version="1.0.9" provider-name="Lunatixz">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.six" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" version="0.1.3.1"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.7.0"/> 
        <import addon="script.module.simplecache" version="1.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.ui.screensaver" library="default.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <source>https://github.com/Lunatixz/KODI_Addons/tree/master/screensaver.google.earth</source>
        <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=321718</forum>
        <news>v.1.0.8[CR]- Matrix compatibility.</news>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/images/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/images/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot01.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot02.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot03.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot04.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
        <summary lang="da_DK">Earth View viser et smukt satellitbillede fra Google Earth...</summary>
        <summary lang="de_DE">Earth View zeigt ein schönes Satellitenbild von Google Earth an …</summary>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Earth View displays a beautiful Satellite image from Google Earth...</summary>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Earth View muestra una bella imagen de satélite de Google Earth...</summary>
        <summary lang="et_EE">Earth View kuvab ilusa satelliidipildi Google Earthist...</summary>
        <summary lang="fi_FI">Earth View näyttää kauniin satelliittikuvan Google Earthista...</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_FR">Earth View affiche une belle image satellite de Google Earth...</summary>
        <summary lang="hr_HR">Pogled zemlje prikazuje prekrasne Satelitske slike s Google Eartha...</summary>
        <summary lang="it_IT">Earth View mostra una bellissima immagine satellitare da Google Earth...</summary>
        <summary lang="nl_NL">Earth View toont mooie satellietbeelden van Google Earth...</summary>
        <summary lang="ru_RU">Earth View отображает красивое спутниковое изображение из Google Earth...</summary>
        <summary lang="uk_UA">Заставка &quot;Earth View&quot; показує красивий супутниковий знімок із Google Earth...</summary>
        <summary lang="zh_CN">地球视图显示谷歌地球的美丽卫星图像......</summary>
        <description lang="da_DK">Earth View er en samling af de smukkeste og mest slående landskaber, der findes i Google Earth.</description>
        <description lang="de_DE">Earth View ist eine Sammlung der schönsten und eindrucksvollsten Landschaften, die in Google Earth zu finden sind.</description>
        <description lang="en_GB">Earth View is a collection of the most beautiful and striking landscapes found in Google Earth.</description>
        <description lang="es_ES">Earth View es una colección de los paisajes más bonitos e impactantes de Google Earth.</description>
        <description lang="et_EE">Earth View on kogumik kõige ilusamatest ja silmatorkavamatest maastikest, mida Google Earthis leidub.</description>
        <description lang="fi_FI">Earth View on kokoelma Google Earthin kauneimpia ja silmiinpistävimpiä maisemia.</description>
        <description lang="fr_FR">Earth View est une collection des paysages les plus beaux et les plus saisissants trouvés dans Google Earth.</description>
        <description lang="hr_HR">Pogled zemlje je kolekcija prekrasnih pejzaža pronađenih na Google Earthu.</description>
        <description lang="it_IT">Earth View è una raccolta dei paesaggi più belli e suggestivi trovati in Google Earth.</description>
        <description lang="nl_NL">Earth View is een verzameling van de meest mooie en indrukwekkende landschappen van Google Earth.</description>
        <description lang="ru_RU">Earth View — это коллекция самых красивых и ярких пейзажей, найденных в Google Earth.</description>
        <description lang="uk_UA">Earth View — це колекція найбільш красивих і яскравих пейзажів, що знайдені в Google Earth.</description>
        <description lang="zh_CN">地球视图是谷歌地球中发现最美丽醒目的景观的集合。</description>
    </extension>
</addon>
