<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="service.pvr.channels.cleaner" version="1.0.0" name="ChannelsDVR PVR Cleaning Service" provider-name="Lunatixz">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" version="0.1.3.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="settings.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <source>https://github.com/Lunatixz/Kodi_Addons/tree/master/service.pvr.channels.cleaner</source>
        <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php</forum>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Clean ChannelsDVR PVR Buffer</summary>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Limpiar buffer de PVR ChannelsDVR</summary>
        <summary lang="it_IT">Pulizia buffer PVR ChanelsDVR</summary>
        <summary lang="ko_KR">ChannelsDVR PVR 버퍼 정리</summary>
        <summary lang="pl_PL">Czyszczenie bufora PVR ChanelsDVR</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_BR">Limpar Buffer de PVR de CanaisDVR</summary>
        <summary lang="sv_SE">Rensa ChannelsDVR PVR-buffert</summary>
        <summary lang="zh_CN">清理 ChannelsDVR 个人录像机缓冲区</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Left unchecked ChannelsPVR backend can eat up storage with leftover live tv buffers. This service cleans all inactive buffers!</description>
        <description lang="es_ES">Si no se controla el backend de ChannelsPVR, puede consumir espacio de almacenamiento con los búferes de TV en directo restantes. ¡Este servicio limpia todos los búferes inactivos!</description>
        <description lang="it_IT">Il backend ChannelsPVR lasciato deselezionato può consumare spazio di archiviazione con buffer rimasti dalla Live TV in diretta. Questo servizio pulisce tutti i buffer inattivi!</description>
        <description lang="ko_KR">선택하지 않으면 ChannelsPVR 백엔드가 남은 라이브 TV 버퍼로 인해 저장 공간을 차지할 수 있습니다. 이 서비스는 사용하지 않는 버퍼를 정리합니다!</description>
        <description lang="pl_PL">Pozostawiony bez sprawdzenia backend ChannelsPVR może zjadać pamięć masową z resztkami buforów TV. Ta usługa czyści wszystkie nieaktywne bufory!</description>
        <description lang="pt_BR">Se não for verificado, o back-end do ChannelsPVR pode consumir armazenamento com buffers de TV ao vivo restantes. Este serviço limpa todos os buffers inativos!</description>
        <description lang="sv_SE">Om ChannelsPVR-backend inte kontrolleras kan den ta upp lagringsutrymme med kvarvarande buffertar från direktsänd tv. Denna tjänst rensar alla inaktiva buffertar!</description>
        <description lang="zh_CN">若不加以处理，ChannelsPVR 后端会因遗留的电视直播缓冲区而占用大量存储空间。本服务可清理所有未活跃的缓冲区！</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">For Personal use; not meant for general use</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="es_ES">Para uso personal; no destinado al uso general</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="it_IT">Per uso personale; non destinato all&apos;uso generale</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ko_KR">일반적인 용도가 아닌 개인용</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Do użytku osobistego; nie jest przeznaczony do użytku ogólnego</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Para uso pessoal; não destinado ao uso geral</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="sv_SE">För personlig användning; inte tänkt för allmän användning</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="zh_CN">仅供个人使用；不用于一般用途</disclaimer>
    </extension>
</addon>